<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Destructring Generators</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2023-01-26T00:00:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>Divided by Plane</title><link href="divided-by-plane.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-01-26T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2023-01-26T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>koohyar</name></author><id>tag:None,2023-01-26:divided-by-plane.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;object class="align-center" data="images/changes.svg" style="width: 640px;" type="image/svg+xml"&gt;xh_string&lt;/object&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="uniform-surfaces"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Uniform Surfaces&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The practice of keeping your etiquette while in circuits makes you pick up
habits you did not use to have before. Idle times need not much conformation.
You keep your base vectors tidy and all else is simply enjoying invariance when
going through transpositions. Nothing requires you …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;object class="align-center" data="images/changes.svg" style="width: 640px;" type="image/svg+xml"&gt;xh_string&lt;/object&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="uniform-surfaces"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Uniform Surfaces&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The practice of keeping your etiquette while in circuits makes you pick up
habits you did not use to have before. Idle times need not much conformation.
You keep your base vectors tidy and all else is simply enjoying invariance when
going through transpositions. Nothing requires you to report your changes. But
momentum days and all the logging fuss along with the excitements of new paths,
new levels and new discrete transformations start to change you in interesting
ways. You grow curious about what might be left of what used to be your
invariance. Others share your enthusiasm and you get more adept at noticing
perturbations, anywhere! You keep checking your logs every half an odd cycle
and discuss with fellows of the same scope. It is mostly simply enumeration,
sure. But fascination with being factorized and put back with smaller residuals
will not leave you for a good while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interesting is how you would still check your base vectors every now and then.
That is to say, despite the growing confidence of keeping multiplications in
tact, and that with no units, it feels somehow pleasant to consider your own
single process from time to time. The tendency to go through all the arithmetic
with solid standard summations, deducing units at every successor operation, and
waiting for yourself to accumulate linearly takes you back to your earlier self
in a nice way, similar to when idle times used to be simply keeping your
invariance; not much of the more complicated and advanced joy of being
factorized with novel encodings to be put back together to see how much of the
world is left on your orbits in order to make sure you are not messing with the scopes of
your fellows in the circuit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe it is the new implementations, or some changes in the semantics of how
actual residuals can be represented; part of new techniques have you store your
results already in arguments instead of a classic recursion. In any case,
the cool and important niceties of more advanced formulations seem to also have
a way of nudging you to check back on your simple column-wise invarinces, just
for yourself. As if you might need them for some other detailed balance, or
possibly another peace of scope for the sake of your own energy levels. It is
happy to notice it. One might also find themselves saving on a lot index work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="blog"></category></entry><entry><title>Specs and Metrics</title><link href="specs-and-metrics.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-11-06T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-11-06T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>koohyar</name></author><id>tag:None,2022-11-06:specs-and-metrics.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;object data="images/plateau.svg" type="image/svg+xml"&gt;xh_string&lt;/object&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="canonical-blocks"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Canonical Blocks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Abstracts should be promoted&amp;quot;, we read early morning on sticker notes around
the terminal. There had been revalations in some partition design and we had
until autumn to read up or start to copy the correct things. Eventually, most of
it would be just checking new stuff …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;object data="images/plateau.svg" type="image/svg+xml"&gt;xh_string&lt;/object&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="canonical-blocks"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Canonical Blocks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Abstracts should be promoted&amp;quot;, we read early morning on sticker notes around
the terminal. There had been revalations in some partition design and we had
until autumn to read up or start to copy the correct things. Eventually, most of
it would be just checking new stuff others had formatted, but it was important
to know that your syntax stays correct.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cool is, that a good part of everything stays the same. But scopes have these
new &amp;quot;views&amp;quot;, from where all the bounding quantifiers look so tidy that you'd
want to leave your own scope for a while and watch the circuitry! By the time
you are back in your own scope most of what you needed to enumerate will have
high-quality residuals attached to it! You can make new sense of your own bounds
and all of this with no numbers: you had a view, you get projections, it is
nicely designed to work with no parallel assumptions. It is pretty fascinating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Autumn is also far away, so there is plenty of room to look around the new
scopes and learn what to copy, what to curry, etc. Formats are not recursive, is
the main point. The rest is good corollary skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But recovering from syntactical problems will be the all new side of it! You end
up worring less about the curries, less hassle with enumeration. Mostly, union
would be worth your while and you get cool and simple shifts that actually work
the way you would understand, instead of simply reducing everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the time everybody gets comfortable enough with the design, eigenstates and
shared scopes will have been all nicely formatted. We'll have less of the
uncalled for painting and zipping, they are shifts and shifts away and recurse
to their own bounds. The arithmetics is difficult, though. But there seems to be
enough number of empty views to try out all the new functions and see how they
map.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="blog"></category></entry><entry><title>Contours Convolve</title><link href="contours-convolve.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-08-28T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-08-28T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>koohyar</name></author><id>tag:None,2022-08-28:contours-convolve.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;hr class="docutils" /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A nice part of the acyclic movement has been the positive feedback they manage
to store, with or without bounds. Fellow partitions manage to align and keep an
identifier for a simplex with many tables. It is nice, because the normal
setting cannot make convex tables. Well, sometimes it would …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;hr class="docutils" /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A nice part of the acyclic movement has been the positive feedback they manage
to store, with or without bounds. Fellow partitions manage to align and keep an
identifier for a simplex with many tables. It is nice, because the normal
setting cannot make convex tables. Well, sometimes it would, environment
variables could pile up with no guarantee to add up. Although, there are all sorts nested
isolation that take care of the gaurantee. Nothing needs to add up, when your bounds are not identified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class="code c literal-block"&gt;
&lt;span class="ln"&gt;25 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="kt"&gt;int&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nf"&gt;main&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;(){&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;26 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;27 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;YYSTYPE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;yylval&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;28 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;YYLTYPE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;yylloc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;29 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;30 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;yylex&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;yylval&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;yylloc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;31 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;return&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mi"&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;32 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;33 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fascinating, how edges never turn out.&lt;/p&gt;
</content><category term="blog"></category></entry><entry><title>Strays</title><link href="strays.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-08-28T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-08-28T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>koohyar</name></author><id>tag:None,2022-08-28:strays.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;div class="section" id="definiteness-no-marks"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Definiteness, no marks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trees overfit. Day one of most integration tests they tell you that. Quite
straightforward. No wonder trunks and trunks of scopes are allowed to eventually pile up
almost anywhere, over a very long time. They all overfit. Testing these stuff is
a merry-go-round. You fasten your formatter …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;div class="section" id="definiteness-no-marks"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Definiteness, no marks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trees overfit. Day one of most integration tests they tell you that. Quite
straightforward. No wonder trunks and trunks of scopes are allowed to eventually pile up
almost anywhere, over a very long time. They all overfit. Testing these stuff is
a merry-go-round. You fasten your formatter and just sit there for a good
complex of fine automaton. Nothing is wrong and table is what you take for
granted. Counting this as work is a task for the tree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the cache reconf is worth the while. You get static parsing for it;
when stuff change, you change with them. Biased, sure, but shift-invariance
gives you better coverage in exchange for... can't seem to recollect, but in
exchange for the overfit guilt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So we get these per relative association. It is often enough for the normalized amusement
and keeps you from getting into spectrum stuff for leizure. Relative association, by
the way, is more a matter of implementation. Not many care about the term. It is
mostly taken as the ability to index and having it (which don't associate).
But sweeps your worries of derivatives, no under-determinism. It has you going
back to it, though. You get faster, more racing conditions to worry about, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep it to good use, get used to static cache, it's there to stay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class="code c literal-block"&gt;
&lt;span class="ln"&gt;25 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="kt"&gt;int&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="nf"&gt;main&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;(){&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;26 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;27 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;YYSTYPE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;yylval&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;28 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;YYLTYPE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;yylloc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;29 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;30 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;yylex&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;yylval&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="o"&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="n"&gt;yylloc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;31 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="k"&gt;return&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mi"&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;32 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ln"&gt;33 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="w"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="p"&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fascinating, how edges never turn out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="blog"></category></entry><entry><title>Blanket Surfing</title><link href="blanket-surfing.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-07-23T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-07-23T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>koohyar</name></author><id>tag:None,2022-07-23:blanket-surfing.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some internal parts of parsers never actually make it. Sad, really. You fade in
and out for a time that could be eons or milliseconds, to no actual end. They
seem to be fine with it. They show around some stuff that look like leaves and
just puff out of …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some internal parts of parsers never actually make it. Sad, really. You fade in
and out for a time that could be eons or milliseconds, to no actual end. They
seem to be fine with it. They show around some stuff that look like leaves and
just puff out of the scope. No trace, no residuals, it works seamlessly;
&lt;em&gt;natural substitution&lt;/em&gt; is what some like to call it. Never gets old for the
small span of time that you are reminded of it during the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, and this with good reasoning and not much articulation, it &lt;strong&gt;does&lt;/strong&gt;
seem a sad life to live.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- :: argc NUM argv TAIL
:fmt:

 .TH "Defragmentation position. Part-time" 9 "cccc-s2-s2" "version 0.3.1" "vacanc"
 .SH DESCRIPTION
 ." [ad goes here]
 .SH ERRORS
 .IP --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their routines are somewhat simpler. If it were not for the cooling system's
stochstic behavior, we would not have even encountered... our scopes would not
have, is what I mean. To us, it seems they are almost always making some small
buzzy noise. Rarely and if you are lucky, your eyes might catch one sitting on
the edge of a scope waiting to puff out. We don't even know if they can actually
see the cache! Your lifetime multiplies by half if you use cache in daily
routines, but to them it is easier to show leaves as passes and traverse what
might as well be the logs! Good to have them around, though. Lazy logger loves
them. They carry their formatters around with them and Lazy log shouts with
confirmation in his old tone of a thousand threads! We don't do that. We know
which is which and could still do without the need to have our formatters with
us all the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Difficult is only rush hours.&lt;/p&gt;
</content><category term="blog"></category></entry><entry><title>Hessian Points</title><link href="hessian-points.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-07-20T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-07-21T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>koohyar</name></author><id>tag:None,2022-07-20:hessian-points.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;img alt="xh_string" src="images/up.png" /&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="the-grid"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;the grid&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;How would you go about linking this my lad?&amp;quot;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Keeping it together, it would take about four scopes, six max&amp;quot;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Uhum...and for the euler term?&amp;quot;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;..., I would not be too sure. I could guess, but the actual number of&amp;quot;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;No, no, of course. You can take your …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;img alt="xh_string" src="images/up.png" /&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="the-grid"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;the grid&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;How would you go about linking this my lad?&amp;quot;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Keeping it together, it would take about four scopes, six max&amp;quot;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Uhum...and for the euler term?&amp;quot;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;..., I would not be too sure. I could guess, but the actual number of&amp;quot;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;No, no, of course. You can take your unit tests to be present&amp;quot;,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Ah, well, in that case it should be...&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ever-lasting rides on the bus never get old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="miscellaneous"></category></entry><entry><title>Salty Seasons</title><link href="salty-seasons.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-07-19T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-07-19T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>koohyar</name></author><id>tag:None,2022-07-19:salty-seasons.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;div class="section" id="tiling"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tiling&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jupyter had been yawning for some days. It used to be quite more exciting to be around him. We used to laugh at the smart jokes he could make while waiting our lines in cache. By the end of your measurements, half of the joke already made sense! It …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;div class="section" id="tiling"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tiling&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jupyter had been yawning for some days. It used to be quite more exciting to be around him. We used to laugh at the smart jokes he could make while waiting our lines in cache. By the end of your measurements, half of the joke already made sense! It was pretty wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until the dusty particles started evaporating around him. The cache had no clue about these small indices. You could not actually do anything standing in there. The particles, well &lt;em&gt;partitions&lt;/em&gt; to be formal and maintain his jokes as well, they had an unsual, acyclicity, if you will. Later on administration built formatters for them only to keep the residuals uniform. Yet, the partitioning seemed just as off-balance. Jupyter had a strong foot in partitions, it is just that nobody needed them that way anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Standardizing the new algebra did not take many days. Cubes were doing their best to provide volume in the scopes, and they could do this without operators! Still, after standardizing, you would have to do all your normals by hand; no local information. You count your co-occurrences. You look at the table. You ask for sigma. Every time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;date
&lt;span class="nb"&gt;echo&lt;/span&gt; Hello!
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It turned out to be the padded sectors, the problem [citation needed]. Dusty particles seemed to have been there to stay, though. The distraction was something we had to get used to. As a result, less jokes. We would of course have a good laugh every now and then when the residual partition is actually canonical. But those happen rarely these days. Doing ortho-normal arithmetic by hand has become hip and scope expansion is rarely needed. Nobody moves, everything stays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="blog"></category></entry><entry><title>Fusebox</title><link href="fusebox.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-06-18T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-06-18T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>koohyar</name></author><id>tag:None,2022-06-18:fusebox.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;div class="section" id="a-parser-any-parser"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;A parser, any parser!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There had been heated arguments near a cache the other day. There was some sort of incident, nothing serious, it was more the cleanup that caused all the heat. See, a blue scope had gotten called by reference. Points in check, parsing complete, nothing lacking. However …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;div class="section" id="a-parser-any-parser"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;A parser, any parser!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There had been heated arguments near a cache the other day. There was some sort of incident, nothing serious, it was more the cleanup that caused all the heat. See, a blue scope had gotten called by reference. Points in check, parsing complete, nothing lacking. However, when pointers started pulling, most of an afternoon's work started loading, almost tangent to the main scope. Nobody paniced, of course. There are routines, checks, reconfs. Nothing is wrong when parsing is complete. But the foresaken non-blue points (Yes, points, not scopes!) started zipping everything around them while everyone else was waiting in stand for the reconf to take place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&amp;gt; saveobj
Checking feature... done.
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now zipping, in case you are not much familiar, does not really change stuff. If anything, it makes it more difficult for the rest of us to move around and we have to keep bumping into one another until something catches us. So when members of your own scope do it, you keep it formal. No unnecassary exchange, no painting, we wait to be caught. But the non-blue points had to panic around and call one zipping mayhem of encodings. Goddamn signal traps were not catching anything. It was no pretty experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Worse is every morning we see hints in shelves asking everyone to keep referring to them as &lt;strong&gt;non-blue points&lt;/strong&gt; until the color shift is back and you can request an actual log. Nobody does it though. By the time you file a log the inherent bunch of left-aligned upright cyclists have turned your whole scope into a shared object, just because some nauseated environment variable &lt;em&gt;did not properly transpose&lt;/em&gt;! It's a waste of free energy to file the logs. It is easier to keep to your format so you don't regress. At least other points won't nerve your scopes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="blog"></category></entry></feed>